brooklynbowl.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy | Brooklyn Bowl

**Last Modified  April 26, 2019**

We at Brooklyn Bowl are connected to you by our love for experiencing live music together. This means that sharing is one of our highest values. But maintaining the privacy of the personal information you entrust to us is just as important. This Privacy Policy explains how we use and share the information we collect through Brooklyn Bowl’s websites (collectively, the “Website”).

As you may be aware, a new European Union law, called the General Data Protection Regulation (or “GDPR”), gives certain rights to individuals in relation to their personal data. To reflect the increased transparency requirements of the GDPR, we will be making some changes to our Privacy Policy and putting in place certain tools to give you additional transparency and control over the personal data we collect and use.

This Website is maintained by The Bowls LLC, which owns and operates Brooklyn Bowl (“Brooklyn Bowl” or the “Company”) for the purpose of providing you with information about Brooklyn Bowl and to give you the opportunity to browse our calendar and purchase tickets to upcoming concerts and events, subscribe to our mailing list, purchase Brooklyn Bowl branded merchandise and E-Gift Cards, read our blogs, participate in ticket contests and submit requests to celebrate your special events at our venue.

We reserve the right to modify or update this Privacy Policy at any time, with or without prior notice to you, for any reason including, without limitation, as laws and technologies change or we add or discontinue certain services or practices. Any such changes to the Privacy Policy will supersede and replace any previous Privacy Policy effective immediately upon posting to this page. It is your responsibility to periodically review the Privacy Policy as posted here for any changes. Your continued use of the Website after the posting of revisions to the Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such changes. For the avoidance of doubt, you should discontinue using the Website if you do not agree with any changes to the Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy, in effect as of the last modified date listed above, supersedes and replaces any and all Privacy Policies previously in effect.

### 1\. What information do we collect?

When you visit the Website, we collect information that can be used to identify you as an individual (personal information), which you provide voluntarily, and information about your usage of our Website (non-personal or usage information), which we collect using cookies and other technologies as you browse the Website.

### 2\. Personal Information

**Registration Information**

If you want to join our mailing list, purchase tickets to a show, purchase merchandise or E-Gift Cards from our online store, participate in any of our contests or promotions, or engage in other activities on our Website, you will need to provide certain personal information to us or our ticketing partners. The specific information will vary depending on the activity and may include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, credit card number and birth date and gender. If you are not interested in participating in such activities, you are still free to browse the Website; however, if you want to interact more deeply with what the Brooklyn Bowl has to offer, you will need to provide us with the required information.

### 3\. Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We also collect non-personally identifiable information that cannot be associated with your personal identity, but gives us data about your location, your computer and how you use the Website. This information may include:

  * browser and device information, including operating system;
  * IP address;
  * date and time you access the Website;
  * geographic location information;
  * information about how you use the Website; and
  * the site that referred you to the Website.

### 4\. Cookies and Other Technologies

We automatically collect, gather and receive information about your activities on the Website in several ways, including through the use of cookies, web beacons and other technologies. For more information on the use of cookies and similar technologies, click here.

Depending on your Facebook account settings, if you access our Website while logged into your Facebook account, you may be authorizing us to advertise to you on Facebook, although Facebook will not share your information with us. If you do not wish to see advertisements from Brooklyn Bowl on Facebook, you will need to adjust your Facebook account settings.

### 5\. What do we use your information for?

You understand and agree that Brooklyn Bowl is the owner of the information it collects, including your Personal Information. We may use this information for any purpose relating to our business, subject to the prohibitions contained in this Privacy Policy. In general, we may use information that we collect about you in the following ways:

  * to fulfill orders for Brooklyn Bowl merchandise and E-Gift Cards;
  * to analyze your use of, or interest in, our content;
  * to communicate with you by email about upcoming concerts and events, and related products or services that we think may be of interest to you;
  * to help us develop and display content and advertising tailored to your interests;
  * to enforce our terms and conditions; and
  * to generally manage our business.

### 6\. Do we share any information with outside parties?

Brooklyn Bowl may share your information about you with its third party partners and advertisers for the limited purposes described herein. In addition, the Company shares corporate ownership with The Capitol Theatre, Relix Media Group and Lockn’ Festival. Accordingly, the Company may disclose your information to its affiliated companies operating these ventures to enable them to market concerts and other events they think you might be interested in. By submitting your personal information, you agree that we and our affiliates can provide you with this information. If at any point you do not want to continue receive email messages from the Company or any of its affiliates, please follow the unsubscribe instructions in the relevant email.

We may also disclose your personal information to third party service providers we engage as contractors or agents to perform services for us, such as providing payment processing and email marketing services. We share information with these contractors only to the extent reasonably necessary for them to perform these services on our behalf, and pursuant to confidentiality obligations.

Brooklyn Bowl’s Website provides you with direct access to our ticketing partner Ticketfly. Our agreement with this company allows us to access certain information, including name, zip code and email address, they collect from you in connection with your ticket purchases.

The Website contains social media widgets, video players and other devices that provide functionality from other third parties including: social media services such as Facebook, Instagram and others; content providers such as YouTube; music services such as Spotify and Pandora; and advertisers and advertising service providers. The placement of these widgets and of advertising units on the Website may permit these third parties to see information about you and your activities via cookies, web beacons and other technologies they place and/or access on your browser or device, even if you do not interact with them. We also utilize analytics tools for social media and advertising management and reporting which similarly access non-personally identifiable information via these technologies, including Google Analytics and Falcon Social.

We may also disclose your personal information if we are legally compelled to do so. In other words, when the law requires it or when we have reason to believe that a disclosure is necessary or appropriate to address potential or actual injury or interference with the rights, property or operations of the Company or others. Finally, if we undergo a merger or acquisition, or sell or otherwise transfer substantially all the assets of the Company or its affiliates, or relating to the Company, your personal information may be transferred to our successor or assign.

We may also share aggregated non-personal information with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for general business analysis purposes. This aggregated data does not contain any personal information.

### 7\. Special Note Regarding Children Under the Age of 13

The Website is not directed to children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not provide any information through the Website or otherwise provide any information about yourself to us. Brooklyn Bowl is not responsible for independently verifying the age of each of its users. Should you, as a user’s parent or legal guardian, become aware that a user who is under the age of 13 has provided Brooklyn Bowl with Personal Information, please notify us immediately by email at privacy at brooklynbowl dot com or by mail at Brooklyn Bowl, Attn: Privacy Officer, 104 W. 29th St, 11th Floor, New York, NY 10001. Brooklyn Bowl will make reasonable attempts to verify the information provided to us by the parent or guardian is accurate, and if it is determined the user is under the age of 13, any gathered information concerning such user will be deleted from our records.

### 8\. Your Options

If at any point you do not want to continue receive email messages from the Website or any of our affiliates, you may opt-out from receiving further emails by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the relevant email. Please allow up to ten (10) business days for your opt-out request to be processed.

### 9\. How do we protect your information?

Brooklyn Bowl takes reasonable administrative and electronic measures designed to safeguard and protect your Personal Information from accidental loss or unauthorized access, disclosure, or use. This may include using technologies such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) and may include one or more firewalls designed to block access from outside our network. Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers in any country where we do business. Although Brooklyn Bowl strives to protect your Personal Information and privacy, no security method or firewall can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error, and we therefore expressly disclaim responsibility and/or liability for the loss, theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of your Personal Information. In the unfortunate event that your Personal Information is compromised, we may notify you by email at the last email address you have provided to us, in a reasonable time under the circumstances and as required under law. Delays in notification may occur while we take necessary measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable integrity to the system, as well as at the legitimate request of law enforcement should it be determined that such notification would impede a government investigation.

### 10\. Additional Information

**California Residents – Your Privacy Rights**

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (“California Customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any unaffiliated third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California Customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described lists if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its Privacy Policy) a policy of not disclosing customer’s personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure or gives customers a mechanism to opt out of having their personal information disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise the right.

We have opted for this alternative approach. Brooklyn Bowl does not disclose users’ Personal Information to unaffiliated third parties without the users’ consent. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of unaffiliated third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at privacy at brooklynbowl dot com or by mail at Brooklyn Bowl, Attn: Privacy Officer, 104 West 29th Street, 11th Floor, New York, NY 10001.
